

# JHOSSYMAR CONTRERAS

WEB DEVELOPER

#### PROFILE

As a Front end developer with six years of experience, I've had the privilege of working across various sectors, including textiles, digital media, healthcare, and technology. My ability to collaborate with multidisciplinary teams and effectively communicate with colleagues from different areas has allowed me to contribute to the success of challenging projects.

## HOW TO REACH ME

Phone number: (503) 6307 0617 Email: chrisj\_contreras@outlook.com

LinkedIn: @jhossyd3v Github: jhossyd3v

#### SKILLS

## **Coding Languages**

Javascript, PHP, HTML, CSS

#### Databases

MySQL, PostgreSQL

#### **Version Control**

Git, SVN

## Frameworks/Libraries/Other

React, SASS, Wordpress, jQuery, Stylus, Pug, Bootstrap, Gulp

#### **Effective Communication**

**Teamwork** 

**Problem solving** 

Leadership

### Languages

Spanish - Native English - Intermediate

#### CAREER SUMMARY

## **Frontend Developer**

JDK Outstanding Technologies | Mar. 2023 to Present

I created custom websites, and actively contributed to structural and design decisions in the team. When reviewing pull requests, I analyze changes to ensure alignment with client requirements and other teams' needs.

#### Web Developer

La Prensa Gráfica | Dec. 2020 to Mar2023

I collaborated with editors, journalists, designers, and cross-functional teams to analyze their needs and provide solutions. My work included designing and creating web apps, interactive graphics, data retrieval, processing, and presentation

## **Software Developer**

Supertex El Salvador | Nov. 2017 to Dec. 2020

I analyzed processes across different areas and designed and developed modules for the program that managed the manufacturing process within the company

#### EDUCATIONAL TRAINING

**Computer Systems Engineering** Universidad de El Salvador

**English Course**Academia Europea